

WEB DEVELOPER

mazejul@gmail.com

+44 (0)7519 265601 www.julien-maze.com github.com/djorak Moved to Scotland 2 years ago after 4 years of experience in web development in France. Highly motivated, hard-working and attentive to details. Always looking for a new challenge. Love new technologies and learning new things.

Experience

2012 – present

Web Developer

BBC (Knowledge and Learning) – Glasgow, Scotland

- Adding new features to BBC Bitesize and iWonder front-end (HTML/CSS, JS, PHP)
- Creating an API to provide personalised data for a mobile application (Node.JS)
- Creating an internal tool using Node.JS, AWS S3 and Redis
- Maintaining and adding features to existing back-end services (Java)

2012 - 2014

Web Developer

Dickson-Constant – Lille, France

- Creating a mobile and desktop interactive UI from static designs
- · Maintaining and evolving the existing websites
- Improvements to a PHP REST API
- UI improvements to an Actionscript 3 awning simulator (Dickson designer)
- Setting up project management tools (SVN, Redmine)
- Setting up and managing dedicated servers (Debian)

2011 - 2012

Web developer

Abase – Brest, France

- Creating an intranet for a newspaper company using Drupal
- Improvements on a bank budgeting application and CRM (Java, GWT)

2009 - 2010

Web developer ("sandwich course")

STDI – Lassay-les-Châteaux France

- Interactive school books for major French publishers.
- Educational apps using Actionscript 3
- Interactive animations using Actionscript 2 & 3

Education

2009 - 2010

Licence (one-year) in Multimedia and Web development

University Institute of Technology, Laval, France

Web development, project management, e-learning, graphic design

2007 – 2009

University Diploma of Technology (two-years) in Communication Services and Networks

University Institute of Technology, Laval, France

Web development, project management, graphic design, Front-End integration, photography, communication theory, networks administration

Skills

- HTML / CSS
- Javascript (ES6) / jQuery
- Node.JS
- Gulp, Grunt, NPM
- · PHP / MySQL
- TDD / BDD (Cucumber)
- Responsive Web Design
- Java

- OS: Windows, Linux, Mac OS
- Tools: Atom, Git / SVN, Adobe Photoshop & Illustrator, JIRA, Confluence, Redmine
- Learning/experimenting with: React, AngularJS 2, Webpack